

Location: Mumbai, India Telephone: (+91) 7303969321

> Email: masterupmanyu001@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/upmanyu-jha/

Professional profile

A learner, Security Researcher, Cyber Ambassador, Penetration Tester, Blogger, Youtuber having experience of more than 1 year in the cyber-Security domain. My expertise, especially Ethical Hacking, Cybersecurity, Social media crimes, Finding Security Bugs/Loopholes in the Websites & Databases. I am seeking a challenging opportunity to manage and lead large projects where my advanced skills, education, extensive training, and few experiences can be fully utilized and where I can expand my knowledge.

Education & qualifications

Sr. No.	Degree	Institute	Board/University	Year	Performance/ C.G.P.A
1.)	B. E	Fr. Conceição Rodrigues College of Engineering	MUMBAI	2019-2023	9.23 (up till 2 nd Year)
2.)	12 th (HSC)	Nirmala Memorial Foundation college of commerce and Science	MUMBAI	2017-2019	65.08%
3.)	10 th (SSC)	Holy Paradise High School	MUMBAI	2007-2017	82.40%

Technical skills

	Programming	Languages
-	1 1 0 5 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1 1	

- HTML & CSS
- C & C++
- Java (Intermediate)
- Python
- JavaScript and ¡Query
- PHP
- NodeJs (Basics)

Database

- MySQL
- PostgreSQL
- Django framework

Ethical Hacking

- **Web Development** Cybersecurity

- Linux

Bug Hunting

- **Bash and Shell Scripting**
- **Penetration testing**
- **Vulnerability Assessment**
- **Documentation**
- Social Engineering and Reverse **Engineering**
- **Dark Web Analysis**
- Malware analysis

Soft skills

- > Leadership
- Public Speaking

- Spiritual Trainer
- **Stress Management**

Volunteering activities

Cyber Ambassador GCPSSI 2021

June 2020 to July 2021

Junior Council

(Fr. CRCE Team Mavericks)

June 2021 to Present

Junior Students Council Fr. CRCE (Assist. Design In-charge)

June 2020 to July 2021

Professional experience

Bugcrowd

Mumbai, India June 2021 to Present

Bug Bounty Hunter (Self-employed)

> Try Hack Me

Mumbai, India June 2021 to Present

CTF Player and researcher

➤ Gurugram Police Cyber Security Summer Internship 2021 (GPCSSI 2021)

Gurugram, Haryana, India

June 2021 to July 2021

April 2021 to September 2021

Intern (Summer Internship 9th Batch)

Gained intense Knowledge and skills in the Topics covered during the internship:

• Gained intense Knowledge and skills in the Topics/fields covered during the internship: • Email Crimes and Investigation • Social Media Crimes and Security • Financial Frauds and Security • Dark Web Analysis • Cloud Security • IoT Security • Ethical Hacking • Ransomware Analysis • Malware Analysis • Crypto Currency Investigation • Cyber Law and IT act • Cyber Crime investigation • Intelligence Operation • Bug Bounty & CTF

Reference: Rakshit Tandon info@rakshittandon.com

▶ Hack The Box

Mumbai, India April 2021 to Present

CTF Player

Cracked 5 machines In Web domain

▶ HackerOne

Mumbai, India April 2021 to Present

Bug Bounty Hunter (Self-employed)

▶ Pie INFOCOMM Pvt.Ltd.

Mumbai, India May 2021 to June 2021

Blockchain (**Internship**)

> Team Abadha Fr.CRCE

Mumbai, India May 2021 to May 2021

Front End Developer

• made attractive front-end using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

WEB SHINE TECH Pvt.Ltd.

Mumbai, India

<u>Back End Developer</u> (Internship)

• Project 1(Jack digitizing): April 2021 to September 2021 Worked as a Complete PHP and MySQL based full stack developer. Created Database Architecture and designed database schema of an e commerce website. Created Admin dashboard with login and registration with session handling. Created User dashboard with login and registration with session handling. Created order and get quote pages and various other tables with a view, update and delete functionalities. Integrated API to get search functionality with all the possible ways to make it user friendly. Integrated Chatbot to help the customers to communicate with admin easily and directly via mail or message. Integrated payment gateway with PayPal and google pay. Created secured backed using PHP scripts and MySQL. Created an Attractive system with complete authentication and hash value based and made it user friendly.

• **Project 2(NISWARTH WEBSITE for IASIS HOSPITAL):** August 2021 to August 2021 Created a Prototype to get this project for the company (and we got it). Learned to dynamically show videos after uploading.

Cyberace Infovision Pvt.Ltd.

Mumbai, India

Python Programming with Project Design (Internship)

January 2021 to March 2021

- <u>Python Programming with Project Design</u> (Internship)
 - Created secured backed using Python and MYSQL
 Created Attractive login and registration system with complete authentication
 - Created Attractive and easy to edit modules and Beautiful Insights using visualization

Technical Projects

	Dynamic Resume/Portfolio using Django framework	May 2021
>	Music Player, GUI Based TIC TAC TOA, E Commerce Website with Visualization	February 2021
>	Secure Website With minimum vulnerability as per OWASP top 10 vulnerability	Present 2021

Achievements

Scored SGPA 10 in Sem 3 of Computer Engineering	May 2021
E-yantra Competition by IIT Bombay (among top 33%)	June 2021

Certificates

Ethical hacking Workshops by IIT Bombay	December 2019
Cybersecurity Course, Verzeo	February 2021
Ethical Hacker Course, Internshala	May 2021
Ethical Hacking from Scratch, z Security, Udemy	June2021
Pentester Lab	Present
Try Hack Me Courses	Present
Python Data Visualization	Present
Web Application Technologies and Django, Coursera	August 2021
CYB003X-Building a Cybersecurity Toolkit, Edx	July 2021

Interests

Interests: Playing: Chess, Volleyball, Throw-ball, Badminton, Karate, Cricket, Football; Playing Guitar, reding books.

Strengths

➤ Fast Learner ➤ Responsible

"References Available Upon Request"

PMANYU JHA